Like I'm not going up there without a
parachute, man. What are you kidding me?
It's good to be here. I flew to get
here. I don't know if anybody's been in
an airplane joke before,
but I flew to get here. You have a
lovely airport there in Salt Lake.
You're not kidding about the Salt Lake.
It's right there by the runway.
It's like, are we landing in the Salt
Lake or are we going to go with the
runway here?
I like it. It scares first-timers. So,
uh
I like what you're doing there. Thank
you for that. Uh
this is a true story. I don't know if
anybody's been in a true story. I
um
I used to be afraid to fly, but I had to
get over it cuz I was dating a girl who
was also afraid to fly. And you can't
have two people in the same relationship
both afraid to fly. It looks ridiculous
when a couple is clinging to each other
screaming, "We're all going to die."
And you're still on expedia.com booking
a flight.
So, we ended up breaking up. We couldn't
have kids. They'd be cowards, right?
They need a Xanax just to sit in their
high chair. Like, "I'm not going up
there without a parachute, man. What are
you kidding me?"
Oh god. So,
uh it's good to be here. I live in LA.
It's just like Utah.
Um it's just it's the same.
We have snow, too. It's a different
snow. Um don't worry about that.
It's terrible, but um
It's good. I I've been doing comedy
there for about 17 years. I get
recognized more from driving Uber and
substitute teaching than I do from
performing. So, that's nice.
Hey, I know you, man. Oh yeah, from one
of the shows I've been on. No, no, no.
You drove me 4th of July to the beach.
It was wonderful. Uh there was traffic,
but you had cute music on. Five stars,
man. So, thanks. All right.
Makes me feel good. Uh god. LA's funny.
California, you know, you live in
California. People you travel, people
say, "Oh, aren't you afraid of the
sharks? What do you do about the
sharks?" I stay out of the water. You
know, that usually does it. Um
the way it works, they don't come get
you. You know, they don't
They don't lure you in, either. They're
like, "Come on, in. The water feels
great, you know?"
No, I I just ate, you know, I have to
wait a half hour.
My mom's going to get upset.
So.
Sharks don't wait after eating. They
don't wait They don't sit and wait for
30 minutes. They just go right on and
swim. That's why they have terrible
relationships with their moms. Um what
was I talking about? So. Uh so, it's
good good you're out. It's you know,
it's a nice evening. There's some
couples here. That's nice. Nothing more
romantic than watching a stranger speak
for an hour and not having to talk to
each other. That's very uh
That's very beautiful. Um
I uh I'm not married. Uh I'm I'm 44.
I've never been married, never been
engaged, don't have any kids, but I'm
just as exhausted as fathers who've done
that. Like
I'm all caught up with you. So, I I'm
here. I'm out of money. I'm out of
energy. I don't know if I'm going to
have any more kids.
So, I feel like one of you.
I'm at the age I'm at least supposed to
be divorced by now, right? I'm at least
supposed to have
Right?
Have one under my belt, you know, just
just to show. People get weirded out.
People get weirded out you tell them.
So, I have to lie to make them feel
better. I'm like, "Oh, I'm just kidding.
I'm divorced with like four kids or
something." And they're like, "Oh,
that's much better." You know.
We thought something was wrong with you.
Now you can join our support group. Come
on in. It's like, "Whoa, okay. What's
going on?" So. Uh being single and
childless isn't a choice. I was born
like this. It's just the natural order,
you know?
Who am I to argue with, you know?
Right?
It's just so natural, man. So natural.
Uh my mom wants me to get married. A lot
of parents want their kids to get
married and have kids. Grandkids are
cute, but they want to see us suffer
like we made them suffer, right? That's
really that's really what Your father
and I did not work hard and sacrifice,
young man, so that you could just date
different women and enjoy your life. Oh,
no, no, no, no, no, no.
You're going to get married and have
kids. Mom, what if I don't love her?
Love has nothing to do with it. Your
father and I stopped loving each other
years ago. We're much happier now, so.
Oh, that sounds good.
Oh, man.
So, it's good. I I You know, I start
dating someone and my mom wants to get
married and have kids right away. She's
like, "Come on. That girl doesn't put
out. Come on. You got to seal the deal
with one of her friends." I'm like,
"Mother, what is going on here?" You
know, this is ridiculous. So, do you
guys have moms?
Okay, you have one or two orphans in the
middle. All right, nice.
So, I tell girls that on a first date. I
was like, "We got to get married right
away and have kids." Like, "Why?" I'm
like, "My mom said, you know, here's a
note." So.
We got to do it. We got to do it. It's
nice. I So, I travel. I pocket called my
mom the other day. You know, your phone
dials from inside your pocket. You don't
know it.
She's like, "Hey, did you mean to call
me?" I said, "No, I pocket called you."
And she said, "Oh, well, your pocket's a
better son than you are." And I was
like, "Oh."
I got to say, that's brutal, so.
Uh, so it's good, you know, you're
working on that relationship for life.
At this point, I think she'd be happy if
I were just gay, you know? She's like,
"Give me something to work with over
here.
I need something to tell my friends,
right?" So, I bring home other straight
guys. I'm like, "This is my lover, you
know?"
And she gets excited, wants us to get
married, works to legalize gay marriage.
The day of the wedding comes, right? We
have to come out of the closet to say
we're straight.
She freaks out. Our friends are like, "I
knew you straights. Look at those
clothes." You know, I was like, "Well,
this is all right."
Doing my best, you know?
My dad's like, "Oh, I dropped 30 grand
on a wedding and I'm never going to see
it." I'm like, "Dad, I thought the
bride's family paid for that." He's
like, "We thought you were the bride."
What the hell is going on here?
Oh my god.
So ridiculous.
I do a Big Brother thing in Los Angeles.
I don't know if that's big in other
areas. I think it's all over the world,
right? They have Big Brother programs.
My little guy is great. He's 65 and
he takes me to movies and ball games and
he just lets me stay out as late as I
want. It's really so much easier
than I thought it would be going into
the thing. So, um
so it's nice. I
enjoy it. So, thank you women and
mothers. If you're a mother if you're a
mom out there, thank you. It's funny
that that that men avoid relationships
more than women when women do the brunt
of it, right? They have the kids. They
communicate. They they keep the
relationship fresh, you know? And but in
the long run, I think kids cling to
their moms more than their dads. I think
in times of trouble, we go to our
mother, you know? There's no such
expression as wait till your mother gets
home, you know? Kids would be like,
"Cool, when's that going to be? Is that
soon?" Uh
somebody who's going to listen, who I
can reason with, who's not going to
swear and throw furniture. That's great.
She is coming though, right? She's
coming?
OH.
WE'RE MORE CONNECTED OVER THE COURSE OF
OUR LIVES. NATURALLY, we're more
connected to our moms. We're more
connected to the person who shoots 100%
of us out of them in pain than we are
the person who shoots out 50% in
pleasure.
Right down the line with that one. Right
down the line.
Uh some of these I know as I'm saying
them, I'm like, "Oh boy, this could get
quiet quick."
Oh man. And cuz cuz moms, you can hold
that over us our whole lives, right?
"Oh, you don't want to run to the store
for me cuz I remember being in labor for
30 hours so you could be here. Okay.
You know.
But dads can never be like, you know,
"Son, it took me 2 and 1/2 minutes of
joy to make you."
Little gratitude would be nice. Little
bit.
I almost had to take my socks off, so.
All right, little pockets here and
there. Interesting. Interesting. All
right. Different taste. Okay.
Eventually, we'll all laugh at the same
joke. For now,
breaking it off by section and very
organized.
Oh, man.
I have siblings with kids. I'm an uncle.
Um obviously
um I'm a stay-at-home uncle. I'd like to
do that part.
You know, you just uh God, they grow up
so fast when you only see them once a
year, you know.
If you're an aunt or an uncle, I tell
you, when you're watching those kids,
you got to keep your eye on them every
single couple of hours. You really, you
know, you guys You look good. Okay,
we'll see you tomorrow.
But I love it. I love it. It's like
being a grandparent, but you didn't have
to go through the work of being a
parent. You can come and go as you
please.
Uh there was a birthday party for my
niece. I went to a pizza place. She had
to go to the bathroom and all the adults
were busy, so I had to take my
6-year-old niece at the time to the
bathroom. And I've never taken a little
girl to the restroom before, your honor.
Um
And I didn't know. I just a total uh you
know, a single idiot mindset of like, I
have no idea. I know somebody's got to
cross the streams here. Somebody's got
to go in the wrong one.
I was like,
Grown women don't want to go into a
men's room, so a little girl can't go
in, which is exactly what I was supposed
to do.
And I'm like, "Honey, what do you go
into the men's or the women's?" And she
says, "Who knows anymore, you know?" And
I was like,
I'm as smart as this girl. Oh my god,
adopted, right?
So, like a dope, I take her into the
women's.
I take her into the women's restroom
thinking I'm fine, right? And women here
already got to communicating when you're
not angry.
Um,
and then you throw anger in there, and
oh boy, that comes out quick. And women
are like, "What are you doing, you
know?" You And I'm like, "What's your
problem? I've got the pass right here,
right?"
Anyway, um,
we got kicked out, and my niece says,
"Oh, men aren't allowed in the women's
restroom?" And I was like, "No, no." And
she said, "Can women go into the men's?"
And I was like, "You know, we don't
mind. It's the darnest thing."
Right, fellas? We're just more
open-minded, I guess.
So, something to learn from. Something
to learn from, ladies.
All right, good.
Um,
making friends and enemies here within
just a few moments. It's really quite
nice.
Uh, it's good. I don't, you know, I miss
being a kid, right? Being a child is
fun. I miss thinking the girls were
gross. Guys, how much money could we
save if we still thought girls were
gross, right? Hey, stranger, buy me a
drink. Oh, sorry, ma'am, you're gross.
Okay.
You give me the willies.
STDs are nothing but cooties. No way.
That I'm not going with cooties, man.
That's some scary stuff, so.
How do you like growing up? I I like the
wisdom that comes with age, you know,
you learn to pick your battles. I used
to look at beautiful women and think,
"Wow, I'd really like to marry her." Now
I see a beautiful woman, and all I think
is, "Oh, her boyfriend must have to put
up with a lot." You know, that looks
That looks painful. All that shopping
and talking and listening and expensive
pets.
It's easier just to be lonely, right?
He's looking at me by myself walking
down the street. He looks so happy. How
does he do it? Teach me. Teach me.
Oh, but uh it's nice, you know. I I was
I got to make out with a girl once who
was so beautiful I could hardly believe
she'd agreed to it. And uh I was so
nervous I kept having to check in with
her every few moments. I'm like, "You're
still good with this, right?" Cuz if I
don't get you to sign off on everything,
I'm in some pretty big trouble here,
right?
And part of me wanted to get married
with her right there and have a kid just
to you know prove that we were ever
together. And my friends would be like,
"No way did you marry and have a kid
with that girl?" And I'd see I'd say,
"What? Look at Look at this half-cute
baby. I mean, come on."
Look at the teeth on that kid.
Come on.
Yeah,
I have big teeth, guys. That's I'll I'll
explain some of these as I go. Um
I have big teeth. Uh I have a big head
and face around it, which is nice. You
don't want one without the other. Then
people like, "Oh, he's got a small
face." No, it's big teeth, small face.
With the With the combo, I'm able to
eliminate that debate and bring world
peace, uh which is
which is nice. So, I do have a big head.
I always have to wear collared shirts,
otherwise I look like the lowercase
letter I.
So.
Yeah, it's good. So.
Uh yeah, so the beautiful girl, we were
together for a little bit and uh we went
to the movies once and uh the guy's
like, "Hey man, sorry, we're sold out.
Beauty and the Beast." And I was like,
"Oh, excuse me. All right. We weren't
We're not here to see that. Shrek."
Um
So, it was a good time. Uh
I But I don't know, maybe someday I'll
do the marriage. I think, you know, I
have plenty of time, right? 44? Okay.
Um
we'll see, you know. It's It's funny.
Women Women often It's funny. Women
often complain
That's it. Yeah, there's no second half
to that.
Only half of you Only half of you. Oh,
really?
Now I got to find the other half.
I will say that women are very
resourceful. You're allowed to stalk us.
We can't stalk you, okay? We call the
cops on you, they're like, "Get over it,
all right? We have a lot of other bigger
problems to deal with."
Uh, you know the day after Alexander
Graham Bell invented the telephone, he
got a call from some woman he was trying
to avoid. He's like, "How'd you get this
number? I just invented this thing
yesterday."
There's not even a second phone. What
are you I
I can't I can't I can't I'm reinventing
telecommunications. What are you
What are you wearing? Yeah, I'm coming.
Okay, very good.
Just text me the address. Text me. See
you tonight.
Uh
Guys, we wouldn't even know if it's
stalking until it's too late, right? The
woman's got the gun pointed at us. We're
like, "Oh, I should have looked into
this, you
But that's how you solve the gun
problem, I think, is just arm the women.
That's it. Just arm the women, because
rarely are they going to shoot you.
They're going to explain to you why
they're doing it.
You think you can learn now? You think
you can put that into practice? Okay,
there's no bullets in this. I just to
match the purse. I just bought it. So,
it's fine.
Um, it's nice.
Uh, some people would rather be in a bad
relationship than no relationship. We
know some of those people, which is a
shame, right? That's like being out of
groceries and instead of going to the
store, you eat the rat poison, cuz it's
the only thing left in the kitchen. So,
go to the store, shop, get some more
food. Oh, no, I'll just eat this. But
you'll die. But I'll be thinner. Oh, so
good. Oh, god.
So.
Oh, man, I keep saying that. I'm sorry.
I don't mean to say it. I'm used to
doing clean comedy, but promo clean is a
different thing. So, if I keep saying
that, I'm sorry.
Uh, it's the it's the altitude. It's
it's affecting me.
You can hit me on the shoulder
afterwards for every time I say it. So,
stick with me.
Um, so it's good. I love it. I travel.
I you know, I lived I went to Japan for
a couple years. It was a good time,
because my grandpa always said, "You
want to be a man, you got to go fight
the Japanese."
What? Like
So, I went over there to the fight and
uh
I missed the war by 50 years, he goes.
I was half a century off, so that was a
little tricky. But, I stayed over there
and I dated a Japanese girl while I was
there and and the program ended, so I
came home and my friends found out. They
said, "Oh,
you had a Japanese girlfriend. Now, you
have an Asian fetish." And I was like,
"No, I have a woman fetish."
And I was living in Asia, all right?
Two and two be four.
That's all right.
All right?
We adjust to our surroundings. Castaways
don't have coconut fetishes, right?
You put a white supremacist in Harlem,
in a week he'll be singing "We Shall
Overcome."
Army shouldn't guard our borders. It
should be our most beautiful women. And
then when the other army shows up to
fight, it's like, "Whoa, what do we have
here? All right. Guns down. Let's go
back to my place. This war is over."
So, I got back from Japan and my friends
are asking me, "Hey, what's China like?"
I'm like, "Well, it's a different
country. Uh
you can't really compare the two. It's
like comparing apples and orange
chicken.
Uh
We're in debt to China. We owe a lot of
money to China. I don't really mind.
I've been in debt to America my whole
life. Let's give somebody else a chance,
right?
Cuz we're not going to be able to
understand the collection notices once
those come in the mail, right?
Is this a bill or a menu for that new
dim sum place? Now, this looks
delicious. Look at all this red ink.
Must be spicy. Okay.
It's going to get to the point someday
we're going to open a fortune cookie and
it's just going to say, "Pay up, man."
Doesn't sound like Confucius. You know,
what's going on here?
We're a little paranoid about other
people coming in uh to the country, you
know, we're already a very international
community all over, right? There's not
one type of food you can't get here in
town.
We're already very international. July
4th, America's birthday, our greatest
day. Right, it's America's obviously
male. If we were female, we'd have to
celebrate from the 4th through the 11th,
the whole week. Um
Very good. All right.
And what do we do? We light up
fireworks. Do we get these fireworks
from America? No, we have to go to
Mexico to buy fireworks from China so we
can celebrate independence from England
while we drink Budweiser, now owned by
Belgium. So, Yankee Doodle Dandy, we're
all in this together. You know what I'm
saying?
Huh.
I wanted to uh I wanted to learn another
language, so I I went to Ireland.
Okay. My friend married a girl from
there, beautiful Irish girl, and we were
there. And the day before the wedding,
uh we were walking through the streets
of Dublin, and this woman had her purse
stolen. Little white guy, little white
legs, he just ran off. And uh
I I was looking I was watching him, and
I had time to think about I was like, I
could catch him. I had time to think
about catching him. Um I'm white, I've
never caught anybody in my life, you
know? And uh and so I run after him, and
I get him. All of a sudden, I'm right
next to him. I'm like, oh, that was
quick. And I get the purse back for the
woman, and she's so appreciative. She
comes up, she hugs me. Her passport's in
there, a bunch of cash.
And she runs off. And something I hadn't
noticed was he had little guys with him,
little buddies that were kind of
blocking us off as we were chasing. I
didn't even notice. I thought they were
chasing him, too. I was wondering why
they were so slow. Um and they all
surrounded me. They were the same
height. They were surrounding me. And
I'm like, oh my god, did I land on a
witch? Like, what happened?
And one of them looks at me, and he's
like, if you ever do that again, we'll
kill you.
And I was like, oh my god, that accent
is so adorable, you know?
It is so cute. But it's, you know, we
took a picture together and uh
We don't do that enough in this country.
Take pictures with the people who just
robbed us, right? We need to do that
more. I was on the news that night.
Crime in Ireland cut 50%. I'm like, "Oh
my god, all the All the crime in America
the one time I stop it, I'm in the
safest country in the world."
But it is a beautiful accent. If you
know anybody from Ireland or if you've
been there, it's just lyrical the way
they speak. And we try to do the accent,
but it never It always turns into a
Jamaican accent whenever Americans Hey
Patrick, top of the morning to ya. Happy
St. Patrick's Day. What?
Aaron go abroad, man. Yeah, I know it's
a shamrock, but do WE SMOKE IT ANYWAY,
MAN?
That's Jamaican, not Ireland. Jamaica is
Ireland, man. It's Southwest Ireland.
You got to look at a map, man. You got
to look at a map. We smoked the map,
man. We smoked it. It was the only paper
we had left. Okay, pal.
We don't get our accents right out of
because we don't go overseas that much,
right? We go state to state for our
vacations. We don't go overseas.
Uh every state now is like its own
country. And a lot more Americans are
moving south, Arizona, Texas, Florida,
California. I don't know if Americans
are moving south for the weather or if
it's cuz as a country we've gotten so
overweight, we're actually sliding down
the planet, guys.
Right?
Just clinging to Texas as we have a few
more nachos down into Mexico, hopping
off at the Panama Canal, all the way to
Eventually we're hanging off the bottom
of the South Pole. Penguins are running
for their lives. I've seen what they do
to turkeys. Go. Go.
Morgan Freeman's narrating, you know?
Ah.
I can joke about chubby people cuz my
dad is white.
So it's all right. It's all right.
My dad is uh I'm mixed race, actually.
My dad is white from uh Michigan and my
mom is white from Ohio. So it's uh yeah,
it's a nice mix. Nice border joke. Some
of you got that. Okay, very good.
Um so, yeah, it's it's fun. But, I I've
never gotten past food. I you know, um
drugs and alcohol aren't really
necessary, you know, when there's Taco
Bell. You know, like I'm sorry. It's
just
It's like, "Now that I've had heroin,
I'm going to get a Mexican pizza, you
know, this looks good." Uh
People are drinking Red Bull vodka? I
don't Is that crazy? They mix energy
drinks with vodka? Two chemicals working
full speed in the opposite direction? If
you like to watch John Mayer open for
Metallica, Red Bull vodka is for you, I
guess.
Keeping people aggressively drunk for 27
straight hours at a time.
That sounds like fun.
Uh I went to college not far from here
in Helena, Montana. I don't know if we
have any Yeah, nobody Okay, there
weren't anybody there, either. All
right.
Nice.
Uh it's just up to 15. You got that exit
up to 15. You got that exit, too. But,
I'd take that one if you're going to
Helena from here tonight. Go out that
exit. You don't want to walk all the way
around.
Um
But, it's a beautiful I love it. We had
I like the summers better than the
winters for some reason. But, we had a
lot of barbed wire tattoos on the arm in
Mont- Montana. There's a lot of barbed
wire tattoo. It comes in handy if you
have trouble with cattle crossing from
your shoulder to your elbow.
That barbed wire tattoo keeps
everybody's property straight, right?
Cows see that, they're like, "I'm not
going near that, you know. Poked my ribs
on it last time, so."
I got a tattoo of some wire cutters on
this arm. I'm like, "I'm going to get
you, you know? Going to get you. Going
to get your livestock."
Lot of avalanches. We have avalanches in
Montana. Only white people die in
avalanches. I don't get that. Every
other race has figured out how to stay
out of the way of snow when it's coming
down a mountain.
Which is funny because we've been around
snow the longest. You know, you'd think
we'd have figured it out. That's why
it's so hard to find any of us. It's
like we're the same color. So, it's
like, I don't know, man. Where are they?
Uh it was a Catholic college. I was
raised uh I was raised Irish Catholic.
I'm not practicing Irish anymore. Um
Uh we played a lot of sports. We used to
pray.
We used to pray I don't know how you
guys are, but we used to pray to God
before grade school football games that
we'd win and we were playing other
Catholic grade schools who were praying
to the exact same God. I don't think God
cares if St. Catherine's Elementary
beats St. Margaret's Elementary, right?
And if so, who are the public school
kids praying to cuz they were kicking
the crap OUT OF US.
THEIR GOD WAS A bad dude. I'm doing the
sign of the cross while Marcus Jenkins
is dragging me across the goal line for
the
fourth time in the first half on his way
to a Division I scholarship after he'd
sign a bonus and he's making more money
in 1 year than I am doing 17 years of
stand-up comedy throughout the United
States of America. So,
but if you follow sports, you know
there's a lot more white coaches than
black coaches even though a lot more
professional athletes are black than
white and it's finally changing, finally
improving. And people always said it's
racism, it's prejudice. That's why
there's so many more white coaches for
so long as opposed to black coaches. And
it's not racism or prejudice. The reason
for so many more white coaches for so
long is because growing up as a white
athlete, we spend a lot more time on the
sidelines than black athletes.
So, then by the time we retire, it's
like, oh yeah, I've seen the game from
this perspective.
I know exactly what I'm looking at.
Yeah, he's going to come around, he
comes under. I've been over here my
whole life. Oh, yeah.
Look at my footprints from childhood.
Uh age 5, 7, 9, 11, 13. I've never been
on that side. What's it like over there?
Oh, my ankle. Oh, okay. Oh,
okay. My ankle.
White coaches know how to win with less.
Black coaches sometimes have
expectations that are too high, right?
Those who can't teach, those who can
can't teach. Michael Jordan could never
coach basketball. He'd be like, "Come on
guys, why is nobody dunking from the
free throw line?" All right?
These are fundamentals. We talk about
this every day in practice. Just jump
over all five guys every time.
Jump up there, stay up there. You know,
there's nothing going on down here. Win
six championships in eight years, play a
second professional sport, get your own
shoe and clothing line, star in a movie
with Bugs Bunny.
It's the pyramid of success. I don't get
it with you guys, right?
I ran track one year in high school. I
played sports. I ran track one year and
uh I was going to finish ahead of a
black guy in track once. I was like, "Oh
my god, I'm going to do it." And
someone's like, "No, man, he already
finished. He's just doing a cool down."
It's bad. So.
Yeah, so
I grew up in the suburbs. A lot of
suburban fathers want their sons to be
professional athletes at all cost. In my
family was football. What what sport
what's the biggest sport here? Football
or basketball?
Football.
Football and basketball.
All right, we'll go with that. Good job,
everybody.
Two people. All right.
Suburban fathers want their sons, you
know these parents, so they want their
sons to be professionals at all cost,
but they they don't marry the right
woman, you know? And my dad did his
part. He was a big guy, he was athletic,
but if you want a son in the big
leagues, you need to marry a big farm
girl, right?
Or a tough inner city girl. Or a big
tough South Pacific Island woman.
When you marry a sweet little Irish girl
who likes musicals,
I
your son might turn out to be a stand-up
comedian. So, that's what happened.
But, my mom was in the arts. She wanted
us playing sports, too. She was worried
about us being nerds.
Uh she was in an organization called
MAD, which is Mothers Against Dungeons
and Dragons.
I went to Kansas City, which is good.
Anybody been to Kansas City? It's very
fun town, very good food, very good
music. And I wanted to go to this
museum.
A baseball museum. It's called the Negro
Leagues Baseball Museum.
It's very quiet in here right now.
And I wanted to go, and I was working
with a black comedian, and I wanted to
invite him, but I didn't know how to
word the invite.
Right? I don't know who's cool with what
words.
So, I was like, "Hey, man,
do you want to go to the baseball museum
here in town?"
And he said, "What What base I said,
"Oh, there's a baseball museum. You You
might You might love it.
He said, "Oh, the Hall of Fame?" And I
said, "No, that's that's in New York.
This is more of a" And he said, "Oh, the
Negro Leagues Baseball Museum?" I said,
"Yeah, that's it. You said it. You said
it. I I just
I didn't say."
He said, "Man, you can say the word
Negro. It's in the title of the
establishment, you know? It's on the
wall." I said, "Okay, well, I've seen
words on walls before that you know,
they don't
And he said, "We got to end the
ignorance. You got to stop. You got to
be able to have a free exchange of
ideas, and you know, it's okay if you're
asking questions. It's the maliciousness
where you get in trouble. Uh and so I
said, "Okay, well do you want to go to
the Negro Baseball Museum?" And he's
like, "No, not with a white guy." So, I
said, "Okay, all right."
All right, well I'm in the ignorance
tomorrow, I guess. Um
but it's good. It's uh it's fun. I do
love uh I love sports. I love I love
playing. I played high school football
here in the United States of America.
And although you're not necessarily
treated like a god, you definitely see
yourself as one. And in our locker, and
we have banners and signs and slogans
everywhere. And one of them, a commonly
known one, read, "Pain is temporary,
pride is forever." And now looking back,
I can't help but think, yeah, pain is
temporary, you know? What a good point.
Well, unless of course it comes in the
form of an anterior cruciate ligament
tear that you suffer in your left knee
after catching a pass going over the
middle on third and long to help seal
the playoff victory and send your team
into the semi-finals for the California
state championship, a game you yourself
wouldn't be able to play in any other
football game ever again for the rest of
your life. Pain isn't so temporary when
that happens. It tends to stick around a
little while. There's not a lot of pride
when the season's over in 6 weeks into
the cold hard winter after football has
long faded from the minds of overzealous
mothers, fathers, and school
administrators who once sang your
praises, you're still on crutches
relearning how to walk. Nobody's
kneeling before you when you're wrapped
in a leg brace with a bloody
staple-infested bandage around your knee
that requires you to cut off a pant leg
of your overpriced rented tuxedo so that
your parentally arranged prom date has
pictures to show her new boyfriend next
year at UCLA. Meanwhile, you're
attending the local junior college
throbbing in pain every time the
temperature drops below 59°.
That's the kind of pride we're talking
about. Thanks, but I'll pass.
All right, I'll be down the hall in
drama where the only pain will be
watching all those wannabe actors battle
it out over the role of Rum Tum Tugger
in the school's mis-adaptation of the
hit Broadway musical Cats.
I'm so cold.
Oh, hey guys. Um
Sorry about that. I uh
I got my hair cut online. Um
earlier this week. Thank you.
She had socks. Socks.
I made a mess. I'm sorry.
But uh no, I do uh I love sports way too
much. It's time. It's time to call it.
Um people think football is so violent,
but I think it actually helps um because
a lot of violent people are at home on
the couch watching football. So
I That's how I justify it in my own
head. And uh cuz people are like, "Oh,
you know, it's gotten so violent in the
country." Like my neighbors fight a lot.
Um there's a lot of crying, broken
glass. And uh the other night it was so
bad it made the hair on the back of my
neck stand up. And I was like, "Oh, I
got to do something. I got to get
involved." Uh so the next day I went to
the barber and I had him cut the hair on
the back of my neck.
And I just I feel so much better uh
about everything. Yeah. So
So yeah, it's just uh like this whole
thing with the my niece was talking
about was like, "Who knows anymore with
the the sexual gender stuff?" And you
wonder it's kind of the Caitlyn Jenner
was kind of the the the leader in that.
If she's happy, I'm happy. If there were
a surgery to become a comedian, I would
do it. Um
And the only reason we know who this
person is is cuz what Bruce Jenner did
in 1976, the Olympic Games, right? Uh he
won the decathlon in Montreal, America's
200th birthday, it was a great time. And
he wins the decathlon, 10 events, right?
And just out of curiosity, I looked at
the scores of the top of the top women
the top women scores from those same 10
events. And in five of the 10 events,
Bruce Jenner finished ahead of the top
women's score.
Right?
My point is, had he not been such a
procrastinator,
five more gold medals, you guys.
Five more gold medals. Don't
procrastinate in life, okay? Call that
person you like, read that book, write
that book, take that vacation.
Otherwise, you're leaving gold on the
table and the Kardashians will steal it.
And uh and I think life's pretty good.
This is a pretty nice community. I think
it's pretty beautiful up here. You enjoy
living up here, guys?
Yeah.
I I would I would hope so. It's pretty
fantastic. You know, on the news, they
would make you believe that the war is
going to end in the next hour. Uh if you
want world peace, turn the TV off, go
take a walk. You know, that's what you
have to do, right? Because there's great
things going on out there. The networks
make a lot of money from fear, all of
them, you know. I think fear should be a
major in college cuz it makes a lot Are
you pre-law? Pre-med? I'm pre-fear. I'm
going to go to fear school after this.
I'm going to make a lot of money.
Cuz they say the world's gotten so
violent. It's got The world never got
violent. There is no God. The world has
been violent since the beginning. Cain
killed Abel, right? Cain killed Abel,
the third person on the planet killed
the fourth person on the planet. We
weren't even able to make it to three
people
before somebody
was a murderer. At one time, a third of
the people on the planet were murderers,
right?
A third of the people in the hood aren't
murderers. A third of the people who own
guns aren't murderers. A third of the
people in jail aren't even murderers.
San Quentin, Folsom Prison, and Alcatraz
are safer than the book of Genesis.
You thought Compton and Baghdad were
tough? Try downtown Eden after the sun
goes down, right?
There was murder and violence at person
three. One couple had two boys who had
the world to themselves and one of them
was claiming this town ain't big enough
for the two of us.
Cain killed 25% of the world's
population.
That's more than Stalin, Hitler, Idi
Amin, Pol Pot, King Herod, Genghis Khan,
the English, Manifest Destiny, typhoid,
cancer, AIDS, cooties, all combined.
Cain killed a third of the people he
knew. What's He knew three people. He
killed one of them.
If you knew Cain, you had a 66 and 2/3%
chance of survival.
There's no such thing as the good old
days. There was no perfect time to be
alive. There was like one good day.
It was half a day.
Adam and Eve were naked,
alone,
in an oasis.
Lunchtime came.
People got hungry.
Apples were eaten.
Boom, Detroit.
THANK YOU GUYS VERY MUCH. HAVE A GREAT
WEEKEND. You're a great audience. Come
out and see us. Thank you. Cheers.